A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33 FA372
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United Community Funds and Councils of America, Inc. - Annual Dinner - New York City, November 30, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 2155)
- Tax Institute of America - Washington, DC, December 1, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2156)
- Tax Institute of America - Washington, DC, December 1, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2157)
- United Cerebral Palsy Association - New York City, December 5, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2158)
  NAR receives Humanitarian Award.
- United Cerebral Palsy Association - New York City, December 5, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2159)
- New York Academy of Sciences - Sesquicentennial Year Ceremony - Hunter College, New York City, December 5, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2160)
- New York Academy of Sciences - Sesquicentennial Year Ceremony - Hunter College, New York City, December 5, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2161)
- New York County Lawyers Association - Annual Bar Dinner - New York City, December 7, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2162)
- New York County Lawyers Association - Annual Bar Dinner - New York City, December 7, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2163)
- United Jewish Appeal - Inaugural Dinner - New York City, December 7, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2164)
- United Jewish Appeal - Inaugural Dinner - New York City, December 7, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2165)
- Republican Governors' Association - Conference - Palm Beach, Florida, December 8-9, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2166)
- Republican Governors' Association - Conference - Palm Beach, Florida, December 8-9, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2167)
- Pennsylvania Society - Annual Dinner - New York City, December 9, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2168)
- Pennsylvania Society - Annual Dinner - New York City, December 9, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2169)
- Joint Chiefs of Staff - New York City, December 11, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2170)
  Dinner honoring present and former chairman.
- Freedoms Foundation and Congressional Medal of Honor Society - New York City, December 11, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2171)
- "Salute to Javits" Dinner - New York City, December 11, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2172)
- "Salute to Javits" Dinner - New York City, December 11, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2173)
- Governor's Conference on Crime - New York City, December 15, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2174)
- Law Enforcement Conference, December 15, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2175)
- Lake Placid Presentation to U.S. Olympic Committee - New York City, December 17, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2176)
- Lake Placid Presentation to U.S. Olympic Committee - New York City, December 17, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2177)
- Erie County Republican Committee - Buffalo, New York, December 18, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2178)
  Testimonial dinner for Ray Lawley.
- Erie County Republican Committee - Buffalo, New York, December 18, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2179)
- Memorial Service for Australian Prime Minister Harold Holt - New York City, December 22, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2180)
- Memorial Service for Australian Prime Minister Harold Holt - New York City, December 22, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2181)
- Town Meetings TV Show, December 26, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2182)
- Speech Calendar 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2183)
- NAR Message to Legislature - Albany, New York, January 3, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 2184)
- NAR Message to Legislature - Albany, New York, January 3, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 2185)
- Republican Assemblymen Reception - Albany, New York, January 2, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 2186)
- Republican Senators Dinner - Albany, New York, January 2, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 2187)
- Appearance Supporting Romney - Manchester, New Hampshire, January 4, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2188)
- Romney Visit - Manchester, New Hampshire, January 4, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2189)
- New York State Women's Legislative Forum - Albany, New York, January 9, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2190)
- New York State Women's Legislative Forum - Albany, New York, January 9, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2191)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (Lodges 517, 1090, 615) - Albany, New York, January 9, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2192)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (Lodges 517, 1090, 615) - Albany, New York, January 9, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2193)
- New York State Agricultural Society - Albany, New York, January 10, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2194)
- New York State Agricultural Society - Albany, New York, January 10, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2195)
- Westchester County Republican Legislators Cocktail Party - Albany, New York, January 15, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2196)
- New York State Association for Mental Health - Annual Legislative Assembly - Albany, New York, January 16, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2197)
- New York State Association for Mental Health - Annual Legislative Assembly - Albany, New York, January 16, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2198)
- Westchester County Republican Committee - New York City, January 25, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2199)
- Westchester County Republican Committee - New York City, January 25, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2200)
- Rockland County Republican Committee - Fund Raising Breakfast - Nyack, New York, January 26, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2201)
- Rockland County Republican Committee - Fund Raising Breakfast - Nyack, New York, January 26, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2202)
- Federation of Women's Republican Clubs of New York State - Conference Reception - New York City, January 26, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2203)
- Federation of Women's Republican Clubs of New York State - Conference Reception - New York City, January 26, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2204)
- New York State District Attorneys Association - Annual Luncheon - New York City, January 27, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2205)
- New York State District Attorneys Association - Annual Luncheon - New York City, January 27, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2206)
- Women's National Republican Club - New York City, January 27, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2207)
- Women's National Republican Club - New York City, January 27, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2208)
- Charles A. Schoeneck Testimonial Dinner - Syracuse, New York, January 28, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2209)
- Charles A. Schoeneck Testimonial Dinner - Syracuse, New York, January 28, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2210)
- 27th Armored Division - Retired Colors Presented to the Governor - Albany, New York, January 29, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2211)
- 27th Armored Division - Retired Colors Presented to the Governor - Albany, New York, January 29, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2212)
- Governor's Plaque Award - Civil Service Commission - Albany, New York, January 29, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2213)
- Governor's Plaque Award - Civil Service Commission - Albany, New York, January 29, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2214)
- Second Interstate Conference on Air Pollution - New York City, January 31, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2215)
- Second Interstate Conference on Air Pollution - New York City, January 31, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2216)
- Governor's Club Dinner - New York City, February 1, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2217)
- Governor's Club Dinner - New York City, February 1, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2218)
- New York State Society of Newspaper Editors - Albany, New York, February 5, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2219)
- New York State Society of Newspaper Editors - Albany, New York, February 5, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2220)
- Albany County Republican Committee - Lincoln Day Dinner - Albany, New York, February 5, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2221)
- Albany County Republican Committee - Lincoln Day Dinner - Albany, New York, February 5, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2222)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars - Annual Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 6, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2223)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars - Annual Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 6, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2224)
- New York State Association of Fire Districts - Annual Meeting - New York City, February 6, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2225)
- New York State Association of Fire Districts - Annual Meeting - New York City, February 6, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2226)
- New York State Association of Towns - New York City, February 6, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2227)
- New York State Association of Towns - New York City, February 6, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2228)
- Statement re: Sanitationmens' Strike - New York City, February 8, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2229)
- Boy Scouts of America - Dawn Patrol Breakfast - New York City, February 8, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2230)
- Boy Scouts of America - Dawn Patrol Breakfast - New York City, February 8, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2231)
- New York State Employees Brotherhood Committee - New York City, February 8, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2232)
  NAR receives award; speech by Secretary of State.
- New York State Employees Brotherhood Committee - New York City, February 8, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2233)
- New York County Republican Committee - Lincoln Day Dinner - New York City, February 10, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2234)
- New York County Republican Committee - Lincoln Day Dinner - New York City, February 10, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2235)
- Nassau County Republican Committee Reception - Garden City, New York, February 11, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2236)
- Kings County Republican Committee - Lincoln Day Dinner - Brooklyn, New York, February 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2237)
- Kings County Republican Committee - Lincoln Day Dinner - Brooklyn, New York, February 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2238)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce - Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 13, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2239)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce - Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 13, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2240)
- Boy Scouts of America - Annual Report to Governor - Albany, New York, February 13, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2241)
- Boy Scouts of America - Annual Report to Governor - Albany, New York, February 13, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2241A)
- Columbia County Republican Committee - Lincoln Day Dinner - West Ghent, New York, February 19, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2242)
- Columbia County Republican Committee - Lincoln Day Dinner - West Ghent, New York, February 19, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2242A)
- American Legion - 49th Annual Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 20, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2243)
  Dinner given in honor of war veterans who are members of the Legislature.
- American Legion - 49th Annual Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 20, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2244)
- New York University - School of Medicine - Alumni Day - New York City, February 22, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2245)
- New York University - School of Medicine - Alumni Day - New York City, February 22, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2246)
- George Romney Campaign - Detroit, Michigan, February 23-24, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2247)
- Rockefeller Visit to Detroit, Michigan (Romney), February 23-24, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2248)
- League of Women Voters - Legislative Conference - Albany, New York, February 26, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2249)
- League of Women Voters - Legislative Conference - Albany, New York, February 26, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2250)
- National Governors Conference - Washington, DC, February 28, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2251)
  Midterm meeting.
- Rockefellers Accept Presidential Dinner Invitation, February 29, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2252)
- Statement on Mid-Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Compact, March 4, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2253)
- Statement on Mid-Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Compact, March 4, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2254)
- New York State Broadcasters Association - Annual Reception and Dinner - Albany, New York, March 5, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2255)
- New York State Broadcasters Association - Annual Reception and Dinner - Albany, New York, March 5, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2256)
- Delaware River Basin Authority - New York City, March 7, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2257)
  Commission reorganization meeting.
- Delaware River Basin Authority - New York City, March 7, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2258)
- Legal Aid Society - Annual Meeting - New York City, March 7, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2259)
- Legal Aid Society - Annual Meeting - New York City, March 7, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2260)
- 3rd International Conference on Urban Transportation - Pittsburg, Pennsylvania, March 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2261)
- 3rd International Conference on Urban Transportation - Pittsburg, Pennsylvania, March 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2262)
- Times-Union - 50th Anniversary Dinner - Brighton, New York, March 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2263)
- Times-Union - 50th Anniversary Dinner - Brighton, New York, March 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2264)
- Visit of Wives of United Nations Delegates - Albany, New York, March 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2265)
- Suffolk County Republican Committee - Huntington, New York, March 13, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2266)
- Suffolk County Republican Committee - Huntington, New York, March 13, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2267)
- Legislative Correspondents Association - Albany, New York, March 16, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2268)
- Legislative Correspondents Association - Albany, New York, March 16, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2269)
- Manhattan College - New York City, March 20, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2270)
  Convocation on racial justice in the New York community.
- Manhattan College - New York City, March 20, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2271)
- United Jewish Appeal - Inaugural Dinner - New York City, March 21, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2272)
- United Jewish Appeal - Inaugural Dinner - New York City, March 21, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2273)
- Canaan Baptist Church - Installation of Rev. Wyatt Tee Walker - New York City, March 21, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2274)
- Canaan Baptist Church - Installation of Rev. Wyatt Tee Walker - New York City, March 21, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2275)
- Campaign 1968 - Statement of Non-Candidacy - New York City, March 21, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2276)
- Not Used (Box 58, Folder 2277)
- Nominating Speech for Senator Javits - Albany, New York, March 26, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2278)
- New York Republican State Committee - Nominating Convention - Albany, New York, March 27, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2279)
- National Broadcasting Company - New York City, March 27, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2280)
  Convention reception of NBC affiliated stations.
- National Broadcasting Company - New York City, March 27, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2281)
- New York Young Republican Club - New York City, March 29, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2282)
  Dinner; NAR represented by Attorney General Lefkowitz.
- New York Young Republican Club - New York City, March 29, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2283)
- Meetings re: Civil Disorders - Albany, New York, April 2, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2284)
- Conference on Reducing Urban Tension, April 2, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2285)
- County Officers Association - 44th Spring Conference - Grossinger, New York, April 2, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2286)
- County Officers Association - 44th Spring Conference - Grossinger, New York, April 2, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2287)
- Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies - Annual Meeting - New York City, April 4, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2288)
- Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies - Annual Meeting - New York City, April 4, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2289)
- Statements re: Death of Martin Luther King, Jr., April 4, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2290)
- St. Patrick's Cathedral - Installation of The Most Reverend Terence J. Cooke - New York City, April 4, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2291)
- Governor's Conference on Youth - New York City, April 5, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2292)
- Governor's Conference on Youth - New York City, April 5, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2293)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. - New York City, April 6, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2294)
  Dinner honoring Harry Van Arsdale.
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. - New York City, April 6, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2295)
- Monroe County Republican Committee - Dinner - Rochester, New York, April 8, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2296)
- Testimony Before Senate Committee on Public Works, Subcommittee on Air and Water Pollution - Washington, DC, April 10, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2297)
- Testimony Before Senate Committee on Public Works, Subcommittee on Air and Water Pollution - Washington, DC, April 10, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2298)
- National Planning Association Luncheon (IBEC) - New York City, April 11, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2299)
- National Planning Association Luncheon (IBEC) - New York City, April 11, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2300)
- Holy Day Greetings, April 13-14, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2301)
- Public Welfare Steering Committee - New York City, April 15, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2302)
- Campaign 1968 - American Society of Newspaper Editors - Washington, DC, April 18, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2303)
- Campaign 1968 - American Society of Newspaper Editors - Washington, DC, April 18, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2304)
- Schoharie County Republican Committee - Dinner - Sharon Springs, New York, April 22, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2305)
- Schoharie County Republican Committee - Dinner - Sharon Springs, New York, April 22, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2306)
- Women in Crime Prevention Conference - Albany, New York, April 22, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2307)
- Women in Crime Prevention Conference - Albany, New York, April 22, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2308)
- Sub-Committee on Executive Reorganization - Testimony on Rising Hospital Costs - Washington, DC, April 24, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2309)
- Sub-Committee on Executive Reorganization - Testimony on Rising Hospital Costs - Washington, DC, April 24, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2310)
- Sub-Committee on Rivers and Harbors - Testimony on Water Pollution, April 24, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2311)
- Sub-Committee on Rivers and Harbors - Testimony on Water Pollution, April 24, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2312)
- Monroe County Republican Dinner - Rochester, New York, April 29, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2313)
- Monroe County Republican Dinner - Rochester, New York, April 29, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2314)
- Campaign 1968 - Announcement of Candidacy - Albany, New York, April 30, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2315)
- Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement - Dinner - New York City, April 30, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2316)
  Governor's speech given by John Lomenzo.
- Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement - Dinner - New York City, April 30, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2317)
- Campaign 1968 - World Affairs Council - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2318)
- Campaign 1968 - World Affairs Council - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2319)
- Campaign 1968 - World Affairs Council - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2320)
- Campaign 1968 - Iowa, May 2, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2321)
  University of Iowa - Iowa City, Iowa Tom Riley dinner - Cedar Rapids, Iowa
- Campaign 1968 - University of Iowa - Iowa City, Iowa, May 2, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2322)
- Campaign 1968 - Tom Riley Dinner - Cedar Rapids, Iowa, May 2, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2323)
- Queens County Republican Committee Dinner - Cancelled, May 2, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2324)
- 7th Annual Governor's Conference on the Aging - New York City, May 3, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2325)
  Lt. Governor spoke in the Governor's place.
- 7th Annual Governor's Conference on the Aging - New York City, May 3, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2326)
- New York State Savings Bank Association, May 3, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2327)
- Minnesota, May 8, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2328)
- Campaign 1968 - University of Minnesota - Minneapolis, Minnesota, May 8, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2329)
- Kansas, May 9, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2330)
- Campaign 1968 - Kansas, May 9, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2331)
  Kansas State College - Manhattan, Kansas University of Kansas - Lawrence, Kansas
- Campaign 1968 - Delegates Meetings and Platform Hearings - Boston, Massachusetts, May 12-13, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2332)
- Narcotic Addiction Control Commission - New York City, May 13, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2333)
  Conference; Attorney General spoke for the Governor.
- Narcotic Addiction Control Commission - New York City, May 13, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2334)
- Rally - Pennsylvania State University - State College, Pennsylvania, May 15, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2335)
- Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania and Baltimore, Maryland, May 16, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2336)
- Harlem River Park Ceremony - New York City, May 17, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2337)
- Campaign 1968 - Rally at University of Florida - Gainesville, Florida, May 20, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2338)
- Campus Rally at Pennsylvania State University - State College, Pennsylvania, May 16, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2339)
- Campaign 1968 - Rally at University of Florida - Gainesville, Florida, May 20, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2340)
- Taping for Kiwanis Club Luncheon - Rochester, New York, May 21, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2341)
- Campaign 1968 - Economic Club of Detroit - Detroit, Michigan, May 22, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2342)
- Campaign 1968 - Economic Club of Detroit - Detroit, Michigan, May 22, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2343)
- Campaign 1968 - Spelman College - Atlanta, Georgia, May 23, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2344)
- Campaign 1968 - Spelman College - Atlanta, Georgia, May 23, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2345)
- Campaign 1968 - Emory College - Atlanta, Georgia, May 23, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2346)
- Campaign 1968 - Emory College - Atlanta, Georgia, May 23, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2347)
- Campaign 1968 - University of South Carolina - Columbia, South Carolina, May 24, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2348)
- Kiwanis Club Luncheon (Taping) - Albany, New York - Cancelled, May 24, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2349)
- Statement - Office of Executive Management, May 27, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2350)
- Campaign 1968 - New York City, May 27, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2351)
  Press conference re: polls, delegates, leaders, Republican Party, etc.
- Statement for PM's - Federal Taxation of Local Government Bonds, May 27, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2352)
- Campaign 1968 - Rally at University of Denver - Denver, Colorado, May 28, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2353)
- Campaign 1968 - Rally at University of Denver - Denver, Colorado, May 28, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2354)
- Campaign 1968 - Albuquerque, New Mexico, May 28, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2355)
  Statement on rural poverty.
- Campaign 1968 - University of Utah Campus Rally - Salt Lake City, Utah, May 29, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2356)
- Campaign 1968 - University of Utah Campus Rally - Salt Lake City, Utah, May 29, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2357)
- Marymount College Commencement - Tarrytown, New York, May 29, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2358)
- Press Conference Transcripts, April 30-May, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2359)
- Czechoslovakia, June 2, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2360)
- Puerto Rican Day Parade - New York City, June 2, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2361)
- Campaign 1968 - Republican National Committee - Portland, Oregon, June 3, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2362)
- Campaign 1968 - Republican National Committee - Portland, Oregon, June 3, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2363)
- NAR Column for Victor Riesel, June 3, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2364)
- Campaign 1968 - Canaan Baptist Church - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, June 3, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2365)
- Campaign 1968 - Rights' Leaders Meeting - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, June 3, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2366)
- American Institute of Architects - New York Chapter - Annual Luncheon - New York City, June 5, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2367)
- Conference of Mayors - New York City, June 5, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2368)
- National Press Club Luncheon - Washington, DC - Cancelled, June 5, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2369)
- New York Republican State Committee Dinner - New York City - Cancelled, June 6, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2370)
- Statement re: Robert F. Kennedy Death, June 5-6, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2371)
- Statement and Questions and Answers by NAR on Death of Senator Kennedy, June 6, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2372)
- Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute Commencement - Troy, New York - Cancelled, June 7, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2373)
- Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute Commencement - Troy, New York - Cancelled, June 7, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2374)
- Campaign 1968 - Allegheny College Commencement - Meadville, Pennsylvania, June 10, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2375)
- Campaign 1968 - Allegheny College Commencement - Meadville, Pennsylvania, June 10, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2376)
- Campaign 1968 - TV Taping at CBS - New York City, June 11, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 2377)
- Campaign 1968 - TV Taping at CBS - New York City, June 11, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 2378)